<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<T3locallangExt>
	<data type="array">
		<languageKey index="gr" type="array">
			<label index="pagetree_overview.alttitle">Επισκόπιση του δένδρου σελίδων</label>
			<label index="pagetree_overview.description">Η Επισκόηση του δένδρου σελίδων παρέχει πληροφορίες σχετικά με τις σελίδες ένος κλαδίου του δένδρου. Αυτές οι πληροφορίες περιλαμβάνουν τους χρόνους εκινήσης-παύσης των σελίδων, ριθμύσεις του cashe κλπ.</label>
			<label index="pagetree_overview.image_descr">Μία από τις δυνατότητες της Επισκόπησης του δένδρου σελίδων
Η επισκόπιση των μονάδων σας δίνει την δυνατότητα να δείτε τι τύπους εγγραφών υπάρχουν στις σελίδες ενώς κλαδιού. Στην εικόνα εμφανίζονται οι εγγραφές για ένα κλαδί και για δύο επίπεδα μέσα.</label>
			<label index="func_0.alttitle">Βασικές ρυθμίσεις</label>
			<label index="func_0.description">Προβάλει μια επιλογή από πεδία με εγγραφές σελίδων που θεωρουνταί ως οι βασικές ρυθμίσεις για τις σελίδες. Αυτά περιλαμβάνουν, ψευδώνυμα, τους χρόνους εκινήσης-παύσης, πληροφορίες για τα δικαιώματα πρόσβασης κλπ.</label>
			<label index="func_0.details">Οι βασικές ρυθμίσεις προβάλονταί με τρόπο που θυμίζει την προβολή του cash και της ηλικίας. Διαφέρει μόνο</label>
		</languageKey>
	</data>
	<orig_hash type="array">
		<languageKey index="gr" type="array">
			<label index="pagetree_overview.alttitle" type="integer">92312309</label>
			<label index="pagetree_overview.description" type="integer">23585608</label>
			<label index="pagetree_overview.image_descr" type="integer">102428178</label>
			<label index="func_0.alttitle" type="integer">44646530</label>
			<label index="func_0.description" type="integer">251798588</label>
			<label index="func_0.details" type="integer">218228585</label>
		</languageKey>
	</orig_hash>
	<orig_text type="array">
		<languageKey index="gr" type="array">
			<label index="pagetree_overview.alttitle">Pagetree Overview</label>
			<label index="pagetree_overview.description">The Pagetree Overview shows information related to pages for a branch of the page tree. This includes start- and stop-times, cache settings etc.</label>
			<label index="pagetree_overview.image_descr">One of the features of the Pagetree Overview module is that you can see what types of records are found on pages in a branch. Here record counts are shown for a page tree branch 2 levels down.</label>
			<label index="func_0.alttitle">Basic Settings</label>
			<label index="func_0.description">Displays a selection of fields from page records which are regarded as foundational settings for pages. That includes aliases, start- and stop times, access restriction information etc.</label>
			<label index="func_0.details">The Basic Settings view resembles the Cache and Age view quite a lot. They are different only by the selection of fields they show.

&lt;b&gt;Batch editing page fields&lt;/b&gt;
You will find multiple edit-icons around the interface. All edit icons in head lines will bring you to an editing dialog where you can change exactly that field for all listed tables! Very useful for batch-editing of say all &quot;Start&quot; times.
If you click the edit icon at the ID numbers of pages you will get straight to the regular editing of a whole page record.</label>
		</languageKey>
	</orig_text>
</T3locallangExt>