<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<T3locallangExt>
	<data type="array">
		<languageKey index="se" type="array">
			<label index=".description">Dethär är backend-administrationens användargrupper som BE-användare kan använda. Dessa begränsar BE-användarnas rättigheter.</label>
			<label index="title.description">Backend-användargruppens namn</label>
			<label index="db_mountpoints.description">Bestäm startpunkter för användarnas sidträd.</label>
			<label index="file_mountpoints.description">Bestäm startpunkter för filhanteringsträdet.</label>
			<label index="pagetypes_select.description">Välj vilka &quot;Typer&quot; av sidor som medlemmarna kan använda</label>
			<label index="pagetypes_select.details">Denna option begränsar vilka sidor en användare kan ta i bruk.</label>
			<label index="tables_modify.description">Välj vilka tabeller en användare kan ändra.</label>
			<label index="tables_select.description">Välj vilka tabeller användarna kan se i listan ('ändra' tabellerna behöver inte fyllas i här också!).</label>
			<label index="non_exclude_fields.description">Vissa tabellfält är som standard spärrade. Dessa fält kan här öppnas för gruppens medlemmar.</label>
			<label index="hidden.description">Spärra en användargrupp.</label>
			<label index="hidden.details">Om du spärrar en användargrupp kommer  de egenskaper, som du ställt in för alla medlemmar i gruppen att begränsas.</label>
			<label index="lockToDomain.description">Fyll i från vilken värddator användaren måste logga in.</label>
			<label index="lockToDomain.details">Ett TYPO3-system kan ha många domain under sig. Denna option säkerställer att användarna kan logga in endast från en viss värddator.</label>
			<label index="groupMods.description">Välj tillbudsstående moduler för gruppens medlemmar</label>
			<label index="inc_access_lists.description">Välj om denna grupp skall kunna använda Sidtyp, Tabell, Modul och Godkända fält.</label>
			<label index="description.description">Fyll i en kort förklaring för användargruppen, gruppens uppgift och vilka medlemmarna är. Detta är endast för internt bruk.</label>
			<label index="TSconfig.description">Tilläggskonfigurering med TypoScript stilvärden (avancerad).</label>
			<label index="TSconfig.syntax">TypoScript stilar utan villkor och konstanter</label>
			<label index="hide_in_lists.description">Denna option förebygger att en användargrupp inte visas i listorna där användargrupper väljs.</label>
			<label index="subgroup.description">Välj de backend-användargrupper som automatiskt ges åt medlemmar i denna grupp.</label>
		</languageKey>
	</data>
	<orig_hash type="array">
		<languageKey index="se" type="array">
			<label index=".description" type="integer">24692837</label>
			<label index="title.description" type="integer">122308063</label>
			<label index="db_mountpoints.description" type="integer">79572288</label>
			<label index="file_mountpoints.description" type="integer">172594607</label>
			<label index="pagetypes_select.description" type="integer">44094257</label>
			<label index="pagetypes_select.details" type="integer">266555079</label>
			<label index="tables_modify.description" type="integer">138526409</label>
			<label index="tables_select.description" type="integer">79180839</label>
			<label index="non_exclude_fields.description" type="integer">17658287</label>
			<label index="hidden.description" type="integer">190841262</label>
			<label index="hidden.details" type="integer">191806419</label>
			<label index="lockToDomain.description" type="integer">139426379</label>
			<label index="lockToDomain.details" type="integer">85223659</label>
			<label index="groupMods.description" type="integer">249603367</label>
			<label index="inc_access_lists.description" type="integer">208224239</label>
			<label index="description.description" type="integer">189455419</label>
			<label index="TSconfig.description" type="integer">211026111</label>
			<label index="TSconfig.syntax" type="integer">185290164</label>
			<label index="hide_in_lists.description" type="integer">169107711</label>
			<label index="subgroup.description" type="integer">244521906</label>
		</languageKey>
	</orig_hash>
	<orig_text type="array">
		<languageKey index="se" type="array">
			<label index=".description">This is the Backend administration user groups available for the Backend users. These determine the access credentials for the Backend users.</label>
			<label index="title.description">Name of the Backend usergroup. The name should be descriptive and can always be changed later.</label>
			<label index="db_mountpoints.description">Define page tree root points for the group members.</label>
			<label index="file_mountpoints.description">Define startpoints for the file folder tree.</label>
			<label index="pagetypes_select.description">Select which 'Types' of Pages the members may set.</label>
			<label index="pagetypes_select.details">This option limits the number of valid choices for the user when he is about to select a page type.
Choice of Page types (doktype) for a page is associated with a) a special icon for the page, b) permitted tables on the page (see $PAGES_TYPES global variable) and c) if the page is a web page or &quot;system folder&quot; type.</label>
			<label index="tables_modify.description">Select which tables the members may modify.</label>
			<label index="tables_select.description">Select which tables the members may see in record lists ('modify' tables does not need to be re-entered here!).</label>
			<label index="non_exclude_fields.description">Certain table fields are not available by default. Those fields can be explicitly enabled for the group members here.</label>
			<label index="hidden.description">Disables a user group.</label>
			<label index="hidden.details">If you disable a user group all users which are members of the group will in effect not inherit any properties this group may have given them.</label>
			<label index="lockToDomain.description">Enter the host name from which the user is forced to login.</label>
			<label index="lockToDomain.details">A TYPO3 system may host multiple websites on multiple domains. Therefore this option secures that users can login only from a certain host name.
Setting this to for example &quot;www.my-domain.com&quot; will require a user to be logged in from that domain if membership of this group should be gained. Otherwise the group will be ignored for the user.</label>
			<label index="groupMods.description">Select available backend modules for the group members.</label>
			<label index="inc_access_lists.description">Select whether the Access Lists for Page type, Tables, Module and Allowed excludefield are enabled for this group.</label>
			<label index="description.description">Enter a short description of the user group, what it is for and who should be members. This is for internal use only.</label>
			<label index="TSconfig.description">User TSconfig: Additional configuration through TypoScript style values (Advanced).</label>
			<label index="TSconfig.syntax">TypoScript syntax without conditions and constants.</label>
			<label index="hide_in_lists.description">This option will prevent the user group from showing up in lists, where user groups are selected.</label>
			<label index="subgroup.description">Select backend user groups which are automatically included for members of this group.</label>
		</languageKey>
	</orig_text>
</T3locallangExt>